[
    {
        "question": "hj",
        "answer": "No answer found. Sent to supervisor.",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:40:29.088112"
    },
    {
        "question": "how was ur day?",
        "answer": "good",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:42:02.670354"
    },
    {
        "question": "kl",
        "answer": "No answer found. Sent to supervisor.",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:47:18.109037"
    },
    {
        "question": "hj",
        "answer": "hj",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:52:07.549898"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T17:23:01.990425"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "downvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T18:20:43.783277"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is your goal?",
        "feedback": "upvote"
    },
    {
        "question": "j",
        "feedback": "upvote"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "feedback": "upvote"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "feedback": "upvote"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T19:01:24.353493"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T19:02:07.307696"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T19:20:16.975104"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T19:33:01.321928"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "downvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T19:48:20.595240"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T20:07:06.844307"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "work",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T20:09:16.021488"
    },
    {
        "question": "how is weather today?",
        "answer": "baarish",
        "feedback": "downvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T20:09:35.722628"
    },
    {
        "question": "hu",
        "answer": "No answer found. Sent to supervisor.",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T23:18:30.303982"
    },
    {
        "question": "ki",
        "answer": "jk",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T23:19:44.556978"
    },
    {
        "question": "hello what are u doing?",
        "answer": "No answer found. Sent to supervisor.",
        "feedback": "upvote",
        "timestamp": "2025-05-06T23:27:14.915102"
    }
]